{
    "subject": "Giuseppe_Colizzi",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "All_the_Way _Boys",
    "human_readable": "Giuseppe Colizzi directed the film All the Way Boys.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9154806733131409,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Giuseppe Colizzi."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9063987731933594,
            "question": "Is Giuseppe Colizzi known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9055134654045105,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Giuseppe Colizzi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8456151485443115,
            "question": "What other films has Giuseppe Colizzi directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8397941589355469,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'All the Way Boys'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5288835167884827,
            "question": "Who are some actors that might have starred in 'All the Way Boys'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4794405996799469,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'All the Way Boys' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41322702169418335,
            "question": "Where was 'All the Way Boys' likely filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41267189383506775,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of 'All the Way Boys'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3911813795566559,
            "question": "When was 'All the Way Boys' released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Giuseppe Colizzi directed the film All the Way Boys.",
            "html": "yago_17956_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of 'All the Way Boys'?",
            "html": "yago_17956_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was 'All the Way Boys' likely filmed?",
            "html": "yago_17956_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'All the Way Boys' likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_17956_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17956_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17956_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17956_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17956_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17956_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17956_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17956_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17956_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17956_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17956_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Giuseppe Colizzi directed the film \"All The Way Boys\" (1972), which supports the statement that Giuseppe Colizzi directed this film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}